http://www.oneway-solutions.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Need Help?
(866) 446-0872
0 item(s)
Cart:
0 item(s)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Login / Create Account
Oneway Solutions
Plastic PalletsNestable PalletsRackable PalletsStackable PalletsFDA Approved PalletsFire Retardant PalletsExport PalletsContainers & BinsCustom & SpecialtyWood Pallets
Pallets by IndustryPharmaceutical PalletsFood & Agricultural PalletsCan PalletsBeverage PalletOcean Freight
PalletsAutomotive PalletsGrocery & GMA PalletsDrum & Spill PalletsAir Freight PalletsRetail & Point Purchase PalletsDairy PalletsPrinting Industry PalletsFlexible Packaging Roll Pallets
Our Pallet Experts
Contact Us
Blog
Request a Quote
Home
Privacy Policy | One Way Solutions
Privacy Policy
One Way Solutions respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information Collected
If you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via the "mail to:" function or filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by Others
This notice addresses only the policy of One Way Solutions' website and not sites that users access via links from our site. One Way Solutions is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
Cookies
One Way Solutions website does not use cookies. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal Information If you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information
One Way Solutions may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy Changes
Please note that One Way Solutions reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of One Way Solutions and is effective as of December 13, 2010. This statement does not create an agreement between One Way Solutions and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
Contact Us
One Way Solutions400 Central AvenueNorthfield, IL 60093Toll Free: 866-446-0872Tel: 847-446-0872Email: info@oneway-solutions.comWeb Address: www.oneway-solutions.com
CONNECT WITH US
DON'T MISS OUT
Get expert tips, new product notifications & exclusive promotions!
Need Assistance?
